{
	"records":[
		{
			"question":"2 x 4 =",
			"answer":8
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 2 =",
			"answer":12
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 5 =",
			"answer":25
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 8 =",
			"answer":16
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 5 =",
			"answer":40
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 4 =",
			"answer":28
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 3 =",
			"answer":27
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 6 =",
			"answer":42
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 4 =",
			"answer":32
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 2 =",
			"answer":20
		},
		{
			"question":"1 x 9 =",
			"answer":9
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 6 =",
			"answer":48
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 4 =",
			"answer":36
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 6 =",
			"answer":30
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 5 =",
			"answer":45
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 7 =",
			"answer":35
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 6 =",
			"answer":48
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 9 =",
			"answer":81
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 5 =",
			"answer":50
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 7 =",
			"answer":49
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 8 =",
			"answer":24
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 5 =",
			"answer":10
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 1 =",
			"answer":3
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 0 =",
			"answer":0
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 1 =",
			"answer":7
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 6 =",
			"answer":24
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 6 =",
			"answer":54
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 10 =",
			"answer":100
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 4 =",
			"answer":16
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 7 =",
			"answer":14
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 1 =",
			"answer":8
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 7 =",
			"answer":56
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 2 =",
			"answer":18
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 8 =",
			"answer":48
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 1 =",
			"answer":2
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 4 =",
			"answer":20
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 9 =",
			"answer":72
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 9 =",
			"answer":90
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 5 =",
			"answer":25
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 8 =",
			"answer":56
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 3 =",
			"answer":12
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 7 =",
			"answer":21
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 4 =",
			"answer":32
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 4 =",
			"answer":36
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 5 =",
			"answer":30
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 10 =",
			"answer":70
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 2 =",
			"answer":16
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 5 =",
			"answer":40
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 6 =",
			"answer":42
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 9 =",
			"answer":36
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 8 =",
			"answer":64
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 0 =",
			"answer":0
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 4 =",
			"answer":20
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 6 =",
			"answer":60
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 1 =",
			"answer":8
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 9 =",
			"answer":45
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 5 =",
			"answer":40
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 1 =",
			"answer":6
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 0 =",
			"answer":0
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 9 =",
			"answer":63
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 4 =",
			"answer":24
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 8 =",
			"answer":40
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 6 =",
			"answer":54
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 0 =",
			"answer":0
		},
		{
			"question":"1 x 9 =",
			"answer":9
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 2 =",
			"answer":16
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 5 =",
			"answer":35
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 7 =",
			"answer":42
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 8 =",
			"answer":72
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 9 =",
			"answer":81
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 3 =",
			"answer":18
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 4 =",
			"answer":28
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 2 =",
			"answer":18
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 7 =",
			"answer":21
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 9 =",
			"answer":63
		},
		{
			"question":"0 x 5 =",
			"answer":0
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 4 =",
			"answer":40
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 10 =",
			"answer":80
		},
		{
			"question":"1 x 2 =",
			"answer":2
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 2 =",
			"answer":6
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 3 =",
			"answer":9
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 6 =",
			"answer":36
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 9 =",
			"answer":36
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 2 =",
			"answer":4
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 6 =",
			"answer":42
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 1 =",
			"answer":4
		},
		{
			"question":"0 x 7 =",
			"answer":0
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 8 =",
			"answer":64
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 5 =",
			"answer":45
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 2 =",
			"answer":12
		},
		{
			"question":"14 ÷ 2 =",
			"answer":7
		},
		{
			"question":"10 ÷ 5 =",
			"answer":2
		},
		{
			"question":"54 ÷ 6 =",
			"answer":9
		},
		{
			"question":"72 ÷ 8 =",
			"answer":9
		},
		{
			"question":"64 ÷ 8 =",
			"answer":8
		},
		{
			"question":"32 ÷ 8 =",
			"answer":4
		},
		{
			"question":"36 ÷ 9 =",
			"answer":4
		},
		{
			"question":"10 ÷ 5 =",
			"answer":2
		},
		{
			"question":"15 ÷ 3 =",
			"answer":5
		},
		{
			"question":"24 ÷ 4 =",
			"answer":6
		}
	]
}